Lars Fallgren had a full working life in the advertising industry behind Sig-
-When it was time to retire.
But the sofa cover did not attract-
-Instället was involved in starting the thunderstorm "rents a pensioner" in Stockholm.
In recent years he has written children's books.
I'm probably an uncle who thinks something should happen in life.
Are the children's chefs happy-
-Above my figures, it pleases me.
My ambition is that it will be a theater in the first step.
I hope so.
It would be great fun to be involved and do it.
Figures from the Pension Authority show that the number of "job sonaries" increased constant-
-In the 2010s.
According to a survey from Jönköping University-
-As every third person over 60 jobonar or plan to be.
In addition to receiving pay, your future pension is also increasing.
For example, one can sit on boards of the company-
-Lite depending on the skills they need.
Are there any risks to continue working as a pensioner?
Yes, there is, of course.
Especially if you work too much.
How are you treated as a working elderly by individuals and society?
Very positive.
We asked the question to several people:
Why do you use us 60-plus?
"It's so safe. You may be a little long, but it's positive and safe."